Kazuto!
Uh, okay, what's with that goofy grin?
Well, this morning I just so happened
to see an interesting article.
And then I noticed that.
Oh, heh heh.
Wow, what are the odds
someone's got a similar handle?
Yeah, except this isn't similar.
It's exactly the same.
If you're gonna put it that
way, then yeah, I guess.
Although, that name's
not really that unusual.
I mean, mine's an abbreviation.
Maybe the Kirito and
GGO's name is... Kiri...
Kirigamine!
Yeah, Toguro Kirigamine or something.
Better eat up or it's gonna get cold.
The resentment will be
presented to you, right?
A pain in the middle of the pain,
I'll know that when the
Oh
I'm going to turn it over to you.
I bet we were trying to kill each other.
Kazuto!
You're making that scary face again.
I hope it's not scarier than usual.
Look, I already know everything.
I know you converted Kirito from ALO to
GGO, so just drop the act already, okay?
Come on,
did you honestly think
I wouldn't notice when
you suddenly vanished from my friend list?
I didn't think you'd check
that thing every five minutes.
I don't. I just knew.
Last night, I got this weird
feeling and checked my list.
When I saw you weren't on it,
I headed over to your room and
was about to bust the door down.
I didn't, because I knew it'd
piss you off something fierce.
I also knew you'd never
quit ALO without telling me.
I figured you must have a good reason,
so I called Asuna up to
see if she knew anything.
You did.
Sorry.
I hope I'm not calling you too late.
It's okay. I wasn't sleeping.
Besides, I...
Never mind.
Honestly, you started to say
something, so just go ahead and say it.
I guess...
I guess I was just thinking about
how I'd like to hear your voice.
That wasn't so hard.
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong. Long day.
Did something happen in the
game you converted over to?
Nothing happened.
It's just...
If the new job's overloading
you, I could help.
Thanks for offering.
I got it, though.
Besides, if you converted
over, you would get lonely.
Are you sure you're alright?
Yeah, I'll be back before you know it.
If you need me, call, okay? Will do.
Good night.
I can't drag Asuna into this.
That guy's sure to show up
in B .O .B.'s main tournament
I have to end this.
This is my problem, not hers.
Kazuto
Know what Asuna told me?
She said not to worry, because once
you tore up GGO, you'd be back.
She didn't say it, but I knew
she was really worried about you.
That makes two of us.
Last night,
you got home so late,
and when I saw your face,
I wanted to say something because you
looked all freaked out. I did? Sorry.
I hope you're not doing anything crazy,
because if you are, I couldn't bear
it if something happened to you.
I'm gonna be fine, I promise.
Tonight's the last night of
GGO's tourney, and after that,
I'll be back to A-L-O and here.
I'll be back no matter
what, so don't worry, okay?
Okay.
Oh, I almost forgot. What?
When I was talking to Asuna,
She just so happened
to tell me that you're
gonna get a huge check from this new gig!
That's right, and when I get back,
I'll treat you to something cool.
Seriously in that case.
There's this awesome
new nano carbon Shino.
I've had my eye on oh
Okay.
Sure you got it!
Dumbass.
He pisses me off?
I'm so mad I could kill him!
Take it easy, Yasuda.
I know you're upset, but it's
weird to see how this worked up.
You saw him.
He's obnoxious, he's cocky,
and he's a dirty liar.
He thinks he's such a big shot fighting
with the sword, and GGO of all places.
He tricked me into thinking he was a girl
and had me take him to the gun market.
I even helped him pick out his gear!
He thinks I'm an idiot!
Oh, man!
It really pisses me off.
What's that look for?
Nothing.
I mean, it's just that, like,
you're acting kind of strange.
I don't think you've ever talked
this much about someone else before.
You're kidding. Really? Yeah.
I mean, you don't usually
let people get to you.
You know, like this.
I get like this when
people push my buttons.
Yeah, I guess you do.
I know how about we find a field
in the game and ambush him huh?
Yeah, I can lure him out
and then you can snipe him.
Although if you want to get him back
you probably want to take him head on.
Either way, I know I can find a couple
machine gunners to back you up if you want.
Thank you, but I had
something else in mind.
It's like yeah, he pisses me off,
but when he fights at least he seems
honorable about it.
Unless I beat him fair and
square, it won't mean anything.
And in today's final,
I'm gonna blow a hole through that dumb
avatar of his if it's the last thing I do.
Would you mind surrendering, then?
I'm not a big fan of slashing at girls.
Just you, wait.
I swear I'm gonna pay you back
double for what you did to me.
What? What's wrong? Nothing.
It's just that...
you see what you're doing?
Wow, I didn't even notice.
I guess it didn't bother
me because I was so mad.
Oh.
Asada.
Wait, what are you doing?
What's the matter?
I'm worried about you, that's what.
You're not acting like
your usual self today.
Oh.
What do you mean?
How do I usually act?
As long as I've known you, you've
been cool, calm, and level-headed.
Nothing gets to you.
You've got the same problems at school as
me, but you didn't run away like I did.
You're, like, really strong.
But I'm not strong at all. You know that.
I get freaked out whenever I see a gun.
But Sinon doesn't.
She's got that amazing rifle
and knows how to use it.
If you ask me, that's who you really are.
And I know one day, you'll be
like that in real life, too.
That's why, when you go ballistic
over that guy, I start to worry.
When I see you lose it like
that, I want to help you.
I'd do anything to help you.
I remember.
I used to be normal once.
I laughed and cried just like anyone else.
I didn't become who I am
now because I wanted to.
Asuna.
I'm sorry.
I really appreciate
you wanting to help me.
Especially since you're
the only one in the city
who really understands
what I'm going through.
But I...
I'm just not ready to be
anyone's girlfriend yet.
Besides, I can't really fix what's
bothering me unless I do it on my own.
I see.
Until then, do you think
you could wait for me?
Thank you.
With that name, and your sword skills,
are you the real deal or what?
Are you Kirito?
Are you Kirito? Are you Kirito?
What's the matter kiddo you
look like you've seen a ghost?
Oh no it's nothing you got
a super hot nurse sitting
here offering free counseling
and you're gonna pass it up?
Come on tell me what's bothering you?
Well since you put it that way I guess
I don't really have a choice do I?
Um, before you came to the rehab
unit, you were in trauma, right?
That I was.
I've got a personal question, and if you
don't want to answer, I totally understand.
Of all the patients you've cared for,
can you remember the ones who died?
Let's see.
I guess if I think about it, I
can recall their faces and names.
Even patients I only spent
an hour or so with in the OR.
Mm-hmm, I remember.
Do you ever wish you could
just forget about those people?
Hmm, that's a tough one.
Not sure if this is an answer,
but it's the best I got.
I guess I think if something's
meant to be forgotten,
a person will end up forgetting it.
Without even thinking they want to.
That said,
the more a person wishes
they could forget something,
the stronger the memory becomes, till
they can't stop thinking about it.
And if that's the case, then maybe
subconsciously, whatever the memory is,
it's something that
shouldn't be forgotten.
Then if I forgot, I must be a monster.
When I was stuck in SAO, I took out.
No, I killed three people.
They were all red players
so murder was their
business and I could have
overpowered them instead
of killing them but I
went ahead and killed
them anyway I did it out
of rage hatred revenge
and over the past year
I've totally forgotten all
about those people even as
I sit here talking about it.
I can't remember what two of them
looked like or what their names were.
How's that possible?
If I can forget people I killed,
what's that say about me? as a person?
I'm sorry, Kirigaya.
I guess I'm not the awesome counselor
I thought I was.
I wish I could take away
the burden you're carrying.
or at least help share the? load of it.
What do I know?
I've never even played sword art online.
When you say you killed someone,
I don't even know what that means.
But, there's one thing I know.
When all's said and done,
the reason you did what you did was
to save someone else, wasn't it?
In the medical field, sometimes
we have to choose who to save.
It doesn't make the decision
to let someone die any easier.
But still,
in a life-or-death situation,
everyone's got the right to consider the
people they can save over those they can't.
Even you.
Just think about the lives
of all the people you saved,
and you'll make peace with your decision.
I don't know.
I don't want to believe you, but...
I can't.
I killed people.
I killed them, and I can't
even remember who they were.
Don't you get it?
It's like I don't even
care that they're dead.
I don't deserve to find any peace!
If you didn't care about what you did,
you wouldn't be suffering like this.
Deep down, you remember.
And when the time's right,
it'll all come back to you.
When it does, and it will.
Just make sure you remember
all the people who were
alive today because you
were there to protect them.
If you need me, call, okay?
um thank you you know for the pep talk
sure i'm glad i could help i don't think
anything will happen till after eight o
'clock i should be out by 10 at the latest
Well, here I go Okie doke, bon
voyage, you super stud, you
Link, start
Asuna
Okay.
I'm going to fight hard.
And I will beat him.
Link, start!
Incoming!
Oh my gosh, Klein! Are you okay?
Come on, guys!
What are you waiting for, an invitation?
He's being extra manly today.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Hang on, Klein, we're coming!
Take your time, ladies!
Don't go! Crap!
Poison gas!
Hold your breath!
Asuna!
Hey! Asuna!
Need a hand here!
Alpine to Asuna! Ah!
Sue, Nila, Hale, Astro!
Yes!
Hey!
I'm sorry, guys.
I didn't mean to space out like that.
Nah, it's all good.
No harm, no foul, right?
Yeah, today's your boy's big day.
That's right, Kirito's tournament.
It's gonna start soon.
I don't know about you guys,
but I say we quit early and get
over to our room to watch it.
I say we use the cash we scored
today to buy beer and snacks.
Do you honestly think we're gonna
let you blow all our money on food?
Don't you worry, Mommy.
Daddy's gonna win today, you'll see.
Sure he will.
No matter where he goes, Kirito
knows how to handle himself.
Hey, guys,
we don't want to miss the first match,
so let's start heading
over to Yggdrasil City.
Okay.
Come on, folks, place your bets.
Xenon!
Hey, Spiegel.
It's almost time.
I believe in you.
I know you're gonna win this thing.
Thanks.
So, what are you gonna do?
Well, I thought I'd find a bar
somewhere and watch the feed from there.
Cool.
I'll track you down after this
and we can toast my victory.
Or cry in our beers.
Sinon.
I mean, Asada.
Yeah, what's up?
I was wondering if you
meant what you said earlier.
What did I say?
You asked me to wait for you, remember?
After you won this thing and
conquered your fears, we...
Then maybe we could go
out and stuff? What the...
You're bringing this up now?
It's just that I care
about you so much, Asura.
Don't do this now.
I have to focus on the tournament.
I'm sorry,
but I don't have a chance of winning
unless I put everything I've got into it.
Right.
I understand.
Even so, I believe in you.
And I'll wait till you're ready.
Okay.
I...
Well, I better go get ready now. See ya.
I'll be rooting for you. Good luck.
I won't lose today.
I won't either!
Thank you.
I don't need one thing to do.
I'm stronger and stronger!
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to cry. I'm going to cry.
See you
next time.
Next time, Bullet of Bullets.